<PluginVersions>
    <LatestVersion>2.8.9</LatestVersion>
    <LatestVersionURL>http://assets.geneious.com/plugins/biocode/Biocode_2_8_9.gplugin</LatestVersionURL>
    <ReleaseNotes>==Biocode Plugin 2.8.9 - 8 June 2015==
* Fixed a bug that prevented the creation of PCR plates from existing 8 strip extraction plates.
* Fixed a problem preventing the use of the same extraction within PCR or cycle sequencing plates.
* Other minor fixes.

==Biocode Plugin 2.8.8 - 2 March 2015==
* The LIMS now actively tries to prevent duplicate extraction barcodes.  It will ask if extractions should be moved if duplicates are detected.
* LIMS data will now be annotated with sequencing primers in addition to PCR primers if using GenBank Submission plugin v1.5.0 or greater.
* Cherry picking an extraction plate will now correctly set the previous plate and well fields.
* Fixed an issue where plates with errors could still be saved.
* Fixed crash that would occur when changing columns in Primer Overview table.
* Fixed a bug that would cause all plates with no workflows to be returned in addition to normal search results when searching solely on FIMS fields.
* Fixed a problem where 8-strip plates would be displayed with incorrect well numbers in some views.
* Fixed a problem where annotating an assembly would prevent generation of a consensus with quality scores.
* Removed the ability to move extraction reactions via the reaction editor invoked from the workflow document viewer.
* Other minor fixes and improvements.

==Biocode Plugin 2.8.7 - 14 January 2015==
* Added modifications in response to upcoming changes that will be made to the Biocode FIMS REST service.
* Added the handling of the presence of duplicate document fields in the FIMS.
* Fixed slow trace downloads from plates without workflows.
* Other improvements and fixes.

==Biocode Plugin 2.8.6 - 12 December 2014==
* Fixed a bug that caused Geneious to crash trying to index sequences or traces that had been downloaded or annotated while using the new Biocode FIMS.

==Biocode Plugin 2.8.5 - 8 December 2014==
* Added cytB to the example loci list.
* Fixed a bug where taxonomy fields that are below the species field on the connection options were not being incorporated into the values of annotated taxonomy fields.
* Fixed a bug where the reporting module could not copy records from FIMS into MySQL based LIMS.
* Other minor fixes.

==Biocode Plugin 2.8.4 - 20 November 2014==
* Remove development changes that were accidentally included in 2.8.3.

==Biocode Plugin 2.8.3 - 19 November 2014==
* Add the ability to bulk add traces to plates of any size.
* Provide more information for connection errors.

==Biocode Plugin 2.8.2 - 28 October 2014==
* Fixed a bug that was causing the Sequencing Primer document note to sometimes not show up on downloaded sequences.
* Fixed a bug where traces downloaded directly from the plate viewer would not be annotated with FIMS information.
* Fixed a bug that caused the FIMS plate to be set as the Sequencing Plate when annotating assemblies using the FIMS.
* Other minor fixes and improvements.

==Biocode Plugin 2.8.1 - 23 September 2014==
* Made 'Forward Plate' and 'Reverse Plate' fields on assembled sequences support more than one value.
* Fixed a bug where workflows were being added to search results when downloading sequences
* Made the 'Mark as Passed' operation work even when links to the original chromatogram documents has been lost.
* Fixed a problem where a background maintenance task would fail when using the Built-in MySQL LIMS.
* Other minor fixes and improvements.

==Biocode Plugin 2.8.0 - 19 August 2014==
* Added '# Passed' and '# Sequences' fields to cycle sequencing plate views.
* Added 'Forward Plate' and 'Reverse Plate' fields to assembled sequences.
* Annotate from FIMS/LIMS now works with any FIMS field in addition to well number.
* Added extraction barcode as a displayable field on all plate types.
* Improved performance when using the Biocode FIMS.
* Fixed a bug where the # Traces field would not be populated in the Tabular Plate View.
* Fixed a bug where searching the Moorea FIMS on Collection Date could return additional results.
* Other minor fixes and improvements.
    </ReleaseNotes>
    <ExtraInformation>
        Upgrading to 2.8.0 will apply a schema fix to MySQL LIMS databases which may take anywhere between a minute and an hour to perform.
        The amount of time depends on the number of traces stored in the database.  If your database has over 30,000 traces
        then it is recommended that an administrator perform it beforehand. Contact support@mooreabiocode.org for instructions.

        Downloading or annotating sequences or traces using 2.8.5 could cause problems for users of the new Biocode FIMS.
        Users of this FIMS should update to 2.8.6 and re-annotate/re-download documents causing errors.
    </ExtraInformation>
</PluginVersions>