<PluginVersions>
    <LatestVersion>3.0.0</LatestVersion>
    <LatestVersionURL>http://assets.geneious.com/plugins/biocode/Biocode_3_0_0.gplugin</LatestVersionURL>
    <ReleaseNotes>==Biocode Plugin 3.0.0 - 9 June 2016==
        * 'BOLD Trace submission': New function to create packages for submission of traces to BOLD.
        * Added the ability to create extraction plates from tissue documents.
        * Search performance improvements.
        * Faster download of sequences.  Download of workflow documents is no longer required when downloading sequences.
        * The # Traces, # Sequences, # Passed Sequences and Sequence Progress fields now show up for workflow documents.
        * Added an operation to the plate bulk editor that allows for the importing of extraction barcodes from FIMS.
        * Added the ability to export tables to .xls, .csv and .tsv.
        * Increased the maximum number of individual reactions from 26 to 30.
        * Added advanded option to New Plate operation for copying reactions to a custom plate format (individual reactions only)
        * Added new Gel Quantification reaction type
        * Download Traces from LIMS can now work on a selection of passed sequences
        * Download Traces from LIMS can now re-assemble traces to selected sequences
        * You can now search for reference assemblies of traces to passed sequences in the Biocode service.
        * Many other bug fixes and improvements.
    </ReleaseNotes>
    <ExtraInformation>
        This version includes an update to the LIMS database format.  This version is not compatible with older versions of the
        LIMS plugin.  All users of the database will need to update the LIMS plugin to the latest version.
        * Built-in MySQL users will be upgraded automatically.
        * Remote MySQL users will need their database administrator to upgrade their database before using this version of the plugin.

        The schema upgrade script can be found at http://software.mooreabiocode.org/index.php?title=Download
    </ExtraInformation>
</PluginVersions>